http://www.norfalco.com/en/Pages/privacy-policy.aspx

NorFalco
EN FR
HomeCurrently selected
About us
ManagementLocationsBeing responsibleSustainable developmentIndustry links
News & Events
TrainingAwards
Products & Services
OverviewQualityCustomer solutionsProduct propertiesProduction process
Storage and handling
General precautionsStorage tanksHandling tank carsOffloading using air
On-line trainingMy H2SO4Contact us
Privacy Policy
Home
NorFalcoHomePrivacy Policy
Site MapTerms of usePrivacy PolicyCurrently selectedCookie policyAccessibilityOur valuesGlencore.com
Page ContentGlencore plc, Baarermattstrasse 3, CH-6340 Baar ("Glencore ", "we" or "us"), has developed this Privacy Policy to explain all our reasonable precautions to keep any personal data ("Data") secure. This website may include hyperlinks to third-party websites, which are completely beyond the control of Glencore. This Privacy Policy only applies to this website and Glencore is not responsible for the content of the privacy practices of third-party websites.This Privacy Policy may be updated without notice. We therefore invite you to return to this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to familiarise yourself with any changes.Processing of data by GlencoreGlencore does not actively collect personally identifying Data from this website except when specifically and knowingly provided by you. While you browse our website, some information may be recorded passively. We do log your internet protocol ("IP") address for purposes of administrating or compiling demographic information and of monitoring usage and performance of this website. We make use of tracking technology ("Cookies") to gather such data as browser type and operating system, metrics, geographical location and understanding how visitors use this website. The recorded data is used anonymously. For more information about cookies, see our Cookie Policy.Data securityWe undertake to take all reasonable steps to prevent your Data from being seen by third parties. We will only disclose your Data to other third parties if required to do so for legal or regulatory purposes.AcceptanceBy visiting this website, communicating with us and submitting your personal data to this website, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way and to the terms of this Privacy Policy.Governing lawThis Privacy Policy is governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive laws of Switzerland. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this website to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Zug, Switzerland.For further information, see our Terms and Conditions
